knok.com 2014-11-22

# Knok - Home Exchange, Apartment Rental and Travel Guide for Families

Introduction

Any use by you of the website operated by Knok Exchange, S.L. at www.knok.com (the 'Site') is conditional upon your acceptance of this Privacy Policy.

All references to 'Knok', 'our', 'us', 'we', 'the Site' or 'company' in this policy refer to Knok Exchange, S.L.

We endeavor to protect your personal privacy. We provide this privacy statement in order to inform you of what we may do with any personal information that we obtain from you. By supplying us with your personal details, you signify your acceptance of our Privacy Statement. If you do not agree with this statement, please do not provide us with your personal details. This privacy statement is incorporated in the Terms and Conditions which govern your use of the Site as a whole. We will use your information for the purposes set out below. You will be given an opportunity to unsubscribe whenever we communicate with you.

We may need to update this privacy statement from time to time. We recommend that you regularly check this page to ensure that you have read the most recent version. 

Legal Age

You must not provide us with your personal information if you are not of legal age to do so in the jurisdiction in which you reside or (if different) in the jurisdiction from which you are accessing the Site. We do not intend to collect personal information from any individuals under the legal age. If we receive notice or believe that someone under the legal age has provided us with personal information we will make every reasonable effort to remove such personal information from our files.

What is personal information?

Personal information is information about an identifiable individual, as defined by applicable law. It does not include aggregated information that does not enable you to be identified, nor does it include business contact information such as your name, title, business address and business phone number.

Collecting Personal Information

You can decide what personal information you provide to us. We will only collect personal information that you choose to provide. Where possible, we will enable you to select how we will use this information, for example, by choosing to opt in or out of receiving information about our future news and promotions.

You may choose to provide us with personal information if, for example, you: contact us with an enquiry; register on the Site as a member; fill out a survey or other form with your personal information; request us to provide you with information; enter a competition; post information to public areas of the Site; or take advantage of a promotion.

You have the opportunity to decide whether or not to receive communications from us at any point where we request information about you.

By providing any personal information to us, you fully understand and clearly consent to the transfer of such personal information to, and the collection and processing of such information in other countries or territories. Any such transfer and processing by us will be in accordance with this Privacy Statement.

In circumstances where you provide us with information relating to any third parties, you affirm that you have received that third party's consent in relation to such disclosure and that the third party has been informed of, and agrees to, our Privacy Policy and the uses which we may make of such information.

Use of Cookies

In common with many websites, we use 'cookies' to help us gather the following information from visitors to the Site. A cookie is a small data file that our server sends to your browser when you visit the Site. The use of cookies helps us to assist your use of certain aspects of the Site. You can delete cookies at any time or you can set your browser to reject or disable cookies. If you do disable cookies, some functions on the Site may not work correctly. We may use information from cookies for the following purposes:

Traffic monitoring e.g:

the IP address from which you access the Site

the type of browser and operating system used to access the Site

the date and time of your access to the Site

the pages you visit

the Internet address of the website from which you accessed the Site

To recognise repeat visitors for statistical / analytical purposes.

Anonymous tracking of interaction with online advertising, for example, to monitor the number of times that a banner ad is displayed and the number of times it is clicked.

We may connect the information that we collect through cookies with other personally identifiable information that you provide to us for the following purposes:

To customize or personalize your experience of the Site so that we can greet you on the Site by name, for example.

For transactional purposes, such as credit card sales.

To monitor your use of our website(s) in order to make our communications to you as relevant as possible; for example, by sending you e-mail communications relevant to parts of the Site that you visit most often or by letting you know about features of the Site that you have not yet accessed.

We may compile and report to third parties (such as advertisers) aggregate statistics about our users in terms of numbers, traffic patterns and related Site information.

Use of information

We will use information collected from you in the following ways:

Transactional Purposes

We may use your personal information in order to respond to your queries and requests and to manage transactions such as credit card payments for any goods or services that you order from us or any of our agents, or for the fulfillment of such transactions. The personal information you provide may be used by an authorized third party to fulfill that order.

Home Exchange

Your non-personally-identifying demographic information and your home details and photos are used to allow other members and visitors to find your home through a search or to check the quality and details of your home. Your contact information (e-mail address and home address) is never made available to other members or visitors; you can choose to provide members with this information yourself, should you wish to do so.

Furthermore, in order to get the most out of our Site as a member, you expressly consent that we use your contact information to regularly forward you travel suggestions according to preference criteria (mainly geographical and temporal) in your profile selected by you.

Marketing communications

We may use your personal information in order to communicate with you about our products and services and those of our subsidiaries, affiliates and parent companies and any of their related businesses. By accepting the Privacy Policy on registration, you expressly accept to receive information about Knok news and promotions. You will also be given the opportunity to unsubscribe whenever we communicate with you, and you may unsubscribe from such communications at any time (see "Unsubscribe, access, questions and further information" below).

Marketing analysis

We may use information for internal marketing analysis. We may also share non-personal information with others, such as advertisers, in aggregate anonymous form, which means that the information will not contain any personally identifiable information about you. We will only share identifiable personal information with third parties for marketing analysis with your consent.

Third party offers

We may arrange for carefully selected organizations to send you marketing and promotional information that may be of interest to you. In such circumstances your personal information may be disclosed to these organizations which agree to be bound by confidentiality obligations and restrictions on use consistent with this Privacy Statement. We will obtain your permission before we send you any such communications.

Public Areas of the Site.

Information or pictures that you post on or via the public areas of the Site are generally accessible to, and may be collected and used by, others and may result in unsolicited messages or other contact from others. Users of the Site are encouraged to exercise caution when providing information about themselves or their homes in public areas of the Site.

Facebook

The Site offers the opportunity for members to access it through Facebook Connect and Google+. We will never post to your Facebook page or Google+ page without your consent.

Sale and Transfer

In the event of a sale, merger, consolidation, change in control, transfer of substantial assets, reorganisation or liquidation, we may transfer, sell, or assign to third parties information concerning your relationship with us, including without limitation, personally identifiable information that you provide and other information concerning your relationship with us.

Administration and data management

We may transfer your personal information to third parties under confidentiality obligations when the performance of any service in relation to the activities above is sub-contracted (e.g. the administration of a marketing campaign).

Legal purposes

We may collect, use or disclose your personal information if permitted by law or required to do so by law or where we believe such action is necessary in order to protect or defend us or other third parties against error, negligence, breach of contract, theft, fraud and other illegal or harmful activity, to comply with our audit and security requirements, and to audit compliance with our corporate policies, procedures, legal and contractual obligations.

Disclosure of personal information

In addition to disclosures outlined in the legal purposes above, from time to time we may disclose personal information to:

  * our service providers and subcontractors, including our affiliates, retained to perform functions on our behalf or to provide services to us, such as warehousing and delivery; marketing and advertising; data processing; software development; website hosting and management; information technology and office services; legal, accounting, audit and other professional service providers; and others, provided such service provider does not collect, use or disclose the personal information for any purpose other than to perform functions, provide services or as otherwise required by law;
  * a person or entity, including our affiliates, to whom disclosure is required in order to fulfill one or more of the purposes described above under "Purposes for collecting information";
  * a person who, in our reasonable judgment, is providing or seeking the information as the authorized or appointed legal agent of the subject individual; or
  * any third party with your consent or where disclosure is required or permitted by law.

Your acceptance of the Terms and Conditions of use of the Site, which include this Privacy Policy, constitutes a granting of consent to the use and disclosure of your personal information for the purposes set out above.

Security

We take security seriously and take precautions to keep your personal information secure. We have installed the appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard the information we collect. However, due to the open communication nature of the Internet, we cannot guarantee that communications between you and us, or information stored on our servers, will be free from unauthorized access by third parties.

Unsubscribe, access, questions and further information

At your request, where the law requires us to do so, we will confirm what personal information we hold about you, update your information, delete your information and/or correct any inaccuracies in such personal information if you contact us using the details provided below.

If you would like to unsubscribe from our communications or if you have any privacy-related questions, concerns or complaints, please contact: [questions@knok.com](mailto:questions@knok.com) .

Links

The Site may contain links or references to other websites outside of our control. Please be aware that we have no control over these sites and this Privacy Statement does not apply to them. We advise you to read the Privacy Statements and Terms and Conditions of linked or referenced sites that you enter.
